STATEMENT

An IT professional with two years of experience in application development, website development, and implementation, I am highly creative and tech-savvy. I am a fast learner and I can quickly research new technology in many ways. I am able to work well in a team-oriented environment and I have many experiences in cooperation as well.

TRAN PHI ANH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

((+84) 941404225

phianh.dev@gmail.com

d 01/01/2000

DaNang, VietNam

Education

2018-2022

FPT University

Very good Bachelor of Software Engineering in Information Technology

Language

Native in Vietnamese

Intermediate in English

Interested

Technologies Developing

Crypto Guitar

Piano Badminton

Honors Awards

Two years at excellent students

Technology Skill

1. Front-End

- 2 years experience and proficiency HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript/Typescript.
- 2 years experience proficiency with ReactJs, Nextjs
- . Worked with Angular, and expertise with React Native.
- Experience in setting up environments, debugging, solving problems.
- +1 year experience with libraries like Ant Design, Bootstrap, Tailwind Css, etc.
- · Responsive devices

2. Backend

- Understanding Nodejs, Express, Apollo Server
- Understanding designing patterns, principles SOLID, DRY and programming techniques like OOP, API/REST, GraphQL, Apollo Server, and Application Developing.

3. Database

- MySQL, MSSQL, MongoDB.
- SQL language, build and manage database.

4. Other

- CI/CD process, Docker, VPS knowledge
- · GIT, tool support git like tortoisegit, sourceTree.

Work Experience

FPT Software | September 2021 - February 2023

Front-End Developer

Corize Inc Vietnam | March 2023 - Present

Front-End Developer

TRAN PHI ANH

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

(+84) 941404225

phianh.dev@gmail.com

d 01/01/2000

DaNang, VietNam

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1. Accounting HRM | FPT Software company

 Website/ System: supported company's customer recording, imported and exported information about the salary for employee,, provided information about the financial position.

Role: Front-End Developer Team Size: 15 Project Type: Company - Outsource

- Responsibilities: Handle task relative to UX/UI and integration API with FE. Join sprint planning, retro, demo. Develop a new story, fixing bugs, and reformatting code.
- Technical: ReactJs, Javascript, Redux, Java, Spring boot, Ant design, MySql...

2. Akadev Low-Code Platform FPT Software company

 Web application/ System: provided components for users to generate their applications (Traditional Web - RestAPI) based on low-code actions.

Role: Front-End Developer Team Size: 18 - 20 Project Type: Company - Product

- Responsibilities: Implemented functions and components based on given requirements. Maintained, fixed bugs, re-skinned, improved
 performance and upgraded old features. Joined sprint planning, retro, and demo. Participated as a User IT to test systems and build
 demos for customers.
- Technical Angular, Typescript, NgRx(Redux), Java, Spring boot, Microservice Pattern, Micro-Front End, MUI, MongoDB, Socket.io, Docker...

3. Kurabun ecommerce - design product

• Web application/ System: sell product and design them

Role: Front-End Developer Team Size: 10 Project Type: Company - Outsource

- Responsibilities: Defined requirements and estimated tasks for each sprint. Built UI following figmar, developed base on the story, developed features and fixed bugs. Reviewed code for other members. Implemented unit test and integration test.
- Technical: Nextjs, ReactJs, Styledcomponent, Nestjs, Typescript...

4. Symliv Project

• Web application: Managed 1 urban area, beach, population, vehicles, rules. It helped to manage entrances, events of the day, violations... through the online registration form in the application and check QR code.

Role: Front-End Developer Team Size: 8 Project Type: Company - Outsource

- Responsibilities: Worked closely with customers' BA to clear requirements. Developed responsive UI/UX for web which based on the
 design. Developed Endpoint. Endpoint Integration. Developed features, fixed bugs, and communicated feature logic with customers.
- Technical: HTML/CSS, SCSS, Typescript, React, React Native, Redux, Nodejs, Apollo Server, GraphQL, MongoDB.

Registration

Dear Sir/Madam,

Thank you for taking the time to read my description and background. I hope that you will give serious consideration to my application for the job. Regarding my skills, I guess some of your expectations may not be met for me, as they aren't usually the focus of my work. If necessary, it will require training time and as a fast learner, I can make sure that you do not have to worry about that. One final thing I want you to know is that I am always willing to study and practice more in order to become the best version. I find your company/team a suitable place for me to develop and make a contribution. Therefore, I hope to have the opportunity to work and dedicate myself to bringing value to your company and your team as well.